Jhal
[Music]
that scientist Dr.
Jhal
that this guy is mines roadways depot investment
Roshan welcome back to my YouTube channel
CNN some problems will discuss it and
you will see your live with kids during
intercourse with as you can see
now husband takes his effective steps from above 1000 and above 1000
till the first child loan belongs to the
pharmaceutical industry and its name
is almost no points upwards with its
help we can take a break volume in it for
some time so if
you can take it on Monday and you
can consider them near 050 or 51911 and
if the first target is good here then you
can maximize your pocket in it by setting your stoploss its second one belongs to the
industry and its
name is and nutrition can be seen on one side
and you can take extra because of which you can
subscribe for 90 and
you can
add 96952 to adopt roti ke logon  You can do this
because this stock is very
much sought after in intraday, so you have to set max
for minute fans here, after this the third one
here, after this, a very good
recovery, this demand was seen once in the square above it,
due to which if the market
here, if you had a
five minute tree at eight, then in this 100
feet
urad bank, then you can split your stock above Hunter feet
and here they
make an appointment with their staff by feeling what is this and this planet and in this
here we have almost 2.5 percent
of water for stock good and this 42% stock,
you have to set a stop loss of 05 2012 on one side,
we will pay a little from the doctors,
you can place your stop loss at 1038,
here first you have to take
and if you talk about stop and above
here, there is one
that indecisive candle confirmation is
seen, that is, both buyers and sellers
MP are very much confused, so if it is at point 00
till it does not do it,
you can take it in this  Enter, you can top it from the top
if you are 100 or so you
can apply it forcefully, for this we
get to see one and see if
you see it swift below 32500 on Monday then
you send a WhatsApp message to 3200 30228
that if you get it on 3232
here then you send a WhatsApp message to 32318 but
you will get to see it, then you
can subscribe and along with subscribing to it, if you
like this video then like and
subscribe to the channel, so you keep
updating it there with
lots of new channels
and you will see the membership details below,
here we provide
you multibagger and
printed along with our model portfolio, so
join quickly if you want to avail all those benefits, till then you will get it
in the next video, thank you so much
that a
[music] has
happened